enzag.com 2013-06-06

# Enzag Privacy Policy - Enzag

At **Enzag.com** , we are firmly committed to the privacy of our users’ personal information. Our staffs, contractors and others who help us operate our web sites follow this policy on privacy and fair information practices for online activities of enzag.com.  This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by www.enzag.com and how it is used. By using this website, you agree to accept this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policy may change over time as discussed below.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.enzag.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Enzag.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Third Party Advertising**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites.

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. Enzag.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Links**  
Enzag.com also links to a wide variety of other sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects your Personal Information.

**Questions or Suggestions**  
If you want to know more or have any questions concerning the privacy policies of Enzag.com, please feel free to contact us at **[admin@enzag.com](mailto:admin@enzag.com).**

  [Article View] : 1959
